[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 20]
[Limin Bookstore] [Cashier]
[HLA Test Report,
Tiedong District People's Hospital]
[Chronicle of a Blood Merchant, by Yu Hua]
This book leaves every reader upset.
What's written seems
like everyday chatter,
but deep down it hides bitterness.
[Hao Jie, 29, patient]
[Liu Yang, 25, patient's boyfriend]
Xu Sanguan isn't exactly smart.
His first blood sale
is just to be part of the crowd.
Then, he does it for his family,
which is understandable.
But what if it was for someone
outside the family?
Everyone is a precious child
to their parents.
If his parents knew
their son risked his life,
they would be heartbroken.
Don't you think so?
[Flowers bloom and wither,
clouds gather and scatter]
[Six Records of a Floating Life]
Why didn't you wait for me?
I wanted to take a walk.
Put this on.
My recent test results are pretty good.
You don't have to be out
with me every time.
You just got a job and must be busy.
Driving the company car out all the time
will reflect badly on you,
if people see it.
I know you hate riding in that car.
Next time, I'll get a cab to pick you up.
I plan to take a few days off
and spend some time at home.
My mom keeps getting sick lately.
Don't come meet me these days.
Are you mad at me?
Then...
Then what do you mean?
H-Have I said anything wrong?
Did my sister talk to you?
Did she?
Please.
I-If there's anything on your mind,
just speak it out.
Beat me or yell at me if you want.
The way you're acting now
is making me nervous.
What exactly do you mean by this?
Liu Yang,
let's break up.
What did you say?
I said...
I want a breakup.
The potatoes...
You're cutting them into strips
that can serve as load-bearing walls.
How should I cut them then?
Thick strips taste better.
Super crispy.
What's that nonsense now?
You're back quite early today.
Wash your hands for dinner.
Want to wash your hands?
Open your mouth.
Why are you lying down?
Did you eat something
at Wan Xiuhua's place?
Your tummy's all puffed out.
I have to eat your leftovers
at every meal.
I want chicken drumsticks.
Slapping your thigh now, aren't you?
Chicken butt also tastes great.
So cunning. You won't let yourself
lose out even a bit.
A grown man can get over whatever
huge obstacles after a nice meal
and a good sleep.
I specially bought
this free-range chicken today.
You're lucky to get to enjoy it.
Have some more.
Juan.
I need to tell you something.
I plan to get married.
I'll soon bring my future wife home
for a proper meeting with you.
Get me the household register.
Don't put Sichuan pepper powder
on the fries next time.
Nobody cooks this way.
Have you thought it through?
Let's have dinner first.
Any discussion can wait till later.
[Name: Hao Jie] [Household Register]
What are you doing?
It's no good if people see us like this.
I don't care who might see us!
Why did you suddenly ask for a breakup?
I just had dumplings at your place
the day before yesterday.
What on earth are you doing?
Won't you go to Shanghai?
Don't you want the money I owe you?
What exactly are you up to?
You must make it clear today!
Or I won't let you leave.
Stop being unreasonable.
My sister talked to you, didn't she?
Anyway, whatever reason there may be,
I refuse to break up with you.
I've loved you since high school.
And I don't plan on changing that.
I know you think you are a burden to me.
But I don't care.
I just want to see you every day.
I'll do anything to keep you around.
Let's get married.
All of these are yours now.
I'll give you anything you want.
I-In the future, I won't keep
a single penny of what I earn.
You can have my all, okay?
Let's get a marriage certificate today.
No, tomorrow.
I don't have my household register
on me today.
What's all this for?
Listen up.
I know this is not fair to you.
I'm poor and I can't afford a ring.
Our money has to be saved
for when we reach Shanghai.
I'll make it up to you
when we get there, okay?
Don't you like taking the train
and hearing the station names?
After you get a kidney transplant,
I'll ride the train with you every day.
We'll travel from south to north,
and from east to west.
I'll read the station names to you
one by one, okay?
Stop messing around.
How am I messing around?
I'm overjoyed
now that I'm getting married.
I-I'm going to have a wife!
I'm thrilled!
I'm going to have a wife!
I'm getting married!
Come on!
Cheers!
Drink up.
What? You had too much to drink?
Go on, guys.
I need to use the restroom.
Where are you going?
Let me check your pulse
to see if you have kidney deficiency.
What's the matter with you?
Whenever it's time to pay,
you always go to the restroom.
I really need to take a dump.
Cut it out!
I paid last time.
And the time before that, Si paid, right?
I absolutely did.
That cost me a fortune.
It should be your turn this time, huh?
Come on.
Nature calls. Can't refute that, right?
I just want to take a dump.
Enough talking to him.
Get in his pockets. Search!
Please don't.
The stuffing's poking
out of my cotton pants.
What? Keep searching, guys!
My sister needs that for her treatment.
You must be kidding me.
What are you looking at?
Hand it to me!
Give me the bankbook.
Keep searching!
Hurry.
There's over 30,000 yuan.
Quick.
Hand it over!
My goodness.
There is really over 30,000 yuan.
What? Are you saving it
for when you get married, lad?
Give it back to me now.
It's for my sister's treatment.
There really is over 30,000 yuan.
Give it back to me!
-Hurry. Give it back to me!
-Sorry, guys.
Well, I need to borrow
San Yan'er for a while.
Look, you guys enjoy the meal.
Enjoy yourselves.
Sorry.
You're not that big,
but you sure jump high.
Messing with me all the time, huh?
They easily cross the line.
Does the Mercedes
before the Golden Imperial
Dance Hall belong to Dong?
Could you borrow it
and let me use it for one day?
I won't do it for anyone,
but you're an exception.
Not only one car, even if
you want ten,
I'll have it done for you.
Give it a break.
What do you mean?
You know me well or what?
Don't you have a car?
Why are you borrowing another?
San Yan'er.
You're going to have a brother-in-law.
Who will that be?
Ignorance really is bliss.
It's right to say he grew up on handouts.
Exactly.
Sir.
Five hundred skewers for this table.
Got it!
Are you trying to kill us with food?
What's this about?
What happened?
What's going on?
Finally manning up for once
and going all out, aren't you?
Get me ten cases of beer.
Drink these fools to death.
Sure thing, no problem. Coming right up.
Wait, what's going on?
Smartening up now, huh?
I'm going to have a brother-in-law.
What's the need to hold back?
Let's drink!
Congratulations!
-Guys.
-So much joy!
Cheers!
You've arrived, buddy.
What took you so long? Traffic jams?
Kind of.
How have you been lately?
Can't complain.
Do you need to count it?
What's the point of that?
It's been so many years.
When have Dong's goods ever gone wrong?
So you do know that.
Look.
Take a seat somewhere.
Let me check the pay.
I'm busy. Make it quick.
Hey, man,
you're not a good friend.
You never come visit me.
And Dong gives my business little support.
Dong is even busier.
Why a new outfit?
Nice belt.
I heard your sister's getting married,
isn't she?
You also know that?
I'll invite you lot
to the celebration.
You definitely should.
Better hold a proper wedding for her.
You'll have to serve
the premium Chunghwa cigarettes then, huh?
Even the mayor's daughter can't
afford to serve those at her wedding.
Aren't I just a small potato?
Stop making fun of me.
You're a big shot here in Tiecheng,
aren't you?
What big shot?
Dong's best, and I come second, huh?
Why not serve
these fake Chunghwa cigarettes
at your future brother-in-law's wedding?
Are you trying to scare me?
So what if I am?
Could Dong possibly sell fake cigarettes?
Hey, why did you flip over my car?